Christmas time is here!
Wow! Thanks, guys.
That sounded amazing.
Hi, I'm Andy Bernard, and I am
the first office Santa ever
to make holiday
wishes come true.
Who's excited to get
their holiday wishes?
Holiday wishes.
What's that, Stanley?
We know exactly what holiday
you're referring to.
It is important to be mindful of all
belief systems at our holiday party.
I've been here 18 years,
and I've suffered
through some weird
thematic Christmases.
A Honolulu Christmas,
a Pulp Fiction Christmas,
a Muslim Christmas,
Moroccan Christmas,
Mo Rocca Christmas
I don't want it.
Christmas is Christmas
is Christmas is Christmas.
I got Stanley tickets to see
Lewis Black for his birthday.
Might not have
been the best idea.
I don't want no
Kwanzaa wreath.
I don't need a dreidel in my face.
That's its own thing.
And who's that
black Santa for?
I don't care.
I know Santa ain't black.
I could care less.
I want Christmas.
Just give me plain
baby-Jesus-lying-in-a-manger
Christmas.
What is the status on my wish?
Fulfilled.
Brought my bicycle so I can be
your designated driver later,
in the event that you drink too much,
which is by no means required.
What about my wish that we
don't have to attend meetings
that degrade our
sense of adulthood?
That, I cannot do.
But I did get you an acre
of property on the moon.
Where, dark side
or light side?
Light side. Is it by the
Sea of Tranquillity?
As a matter of fact, yes.
Directly adjacent.
Beachfront.
Thank you, Andy.
So whose wish is next?
What about Santa's wish?
My biggest wish is that you all
get along well with Jessica.
Come on, guys, Jessica.
Jim, tell them who Jessica is.
She's not your grandmother,
is she?
Gam-Gam's
name is Ruth, Jim.
You should know. I introduced
you on speakerphone that time.
Jessica is my super
serious girlfriend,
who is seriously awesome
and seriously sexy.
Only thing that's not serious,
by the way, our repartee.
That's great.
When you know, you know.
Hey, what's Ruth's deal, man?
Totally out of your league.
So, in summation, ho ho ho,
please be nice to Jessica,
and mistletoe
is not an excuse
for sexual assault.
And don't go near Gam-Gam.
I love Jessica, and I
haven't even met her yet.
It's like, we don't
even need to meet, you know?
I already love you. Stay home.
I just want you to
know that I will be mean
to Jessica,
if you want me to be.
Oh, no, no, it's fine, Kelly.
It's really no problem. I was already
planning on being mean to her.
That's okay,
I don't want you to do that.
Hello.
Merry Christmas, Erin.
Kelly, happy Pancha Ganapati.
Ew. What is that?
The five day Hindu
celebration in December,
honoring the god Ganesh,
patron of the arts.
Cool.
Hey, man.
Hey.
How you holding up?
Because of your
wife leaving you.
Kevin.
I actually appreciate
the human intimacy.
I feel like a kitten
being cradled by a gorilla.
Yeah.
It's been 10 days since I
had sexual intercourse.
Well, you came to the right place.
It... This party
will cheer you right up.
I hope so. The corporate
party was wretched.
I am so tired of
the Black Eyed Peas.
It's rock and roll for people
who don't like rock and roll.
It's rap for people
who don't like rap.
It's pop for people
who don't like pop.
Ah.
Heartbreaking.
Oh. Thank you.
Well, I hate to have to take my Santa
hat off and put on my hard ass hat,
but this is serious.
It's come to my attention that
somebody who shall remain nameless
wants to switch desk clumps.
Fine with me. Jim can
leave any time he wants.
Good-bye.
Wasn't me.
It wasn't either of you.
Cathy wants to
leave our clump?
Don't look.
Who it was is not important.
But she did say that
your constant pranking
and one-upsmanship
is driving her crazy.
She or he. I just want to
say this is not my fault.
Okay, the weak
always bully the strong,
contrary to what
you see in the media.
I am always
acting in self-defense.
Occasionally
preemptive self-defense.
Ow! What are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
Respect the hat.
Pam never seemed
to have a problem with us.
All right. I'm gonna speak in a
language you both understand.
Moe-nay.
What was it?
What is it?
Money.
You both have sizable Christmas
bonuses coming your way.
If I catch either of you
messing with the other,
I will give both
bonuses to the other person.
Can't do that.
No, absolutely not.
You need consequences. Okay, I want
you both walking on eggshells.
Hi, I'm Jessica.
I'm looking for Andy.
Jessica, yes.
We don't say hi. We hug.
I'm Erin. Sorry.
Ooh!
I hope you feel really welcome.
We all want you here.
Oh.
My ex is meeting my sex.
Which is always scary.
You know? And not just because you think
they might talk about your penis.
That's just part of it.
Hey! Jess, Erin.
I hope you're not
talking about my penis.
Hi.
Hey, everyone,
I want you to meet Jessica.
She is an assistant cross-country
coach at Bryn Mawr.
Wow.
Erin, by the way,
amazing receptionist.
Oh, that's great.
Backbone of the office.
Which is funny, actually,
because my spine is a mess.
What?
Oh.
Scoliosis. Had to wear a back brace
for three years, but I never did.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, it's kicking in.
Spontaneous scoliosis.
Oh.
This thing could take your
arm off, your head off.
You know,
just exercise caution.
Thank you.
All right.
Oh, yeah,
and there's a Christmas party upstairs
tonight I wanted to tell you about.
Isn't that just
for popsicles?
Popsicles?
Yeah, like, upstairs people. 'Cause
you got a stick up your butt.
Ah. See, I thought it was
because they're all so rich
they could eat popsicles all the time.
What?
I... In my...
Well, you should definitely come.
The foreman always comes.
Plus it's fun, you know,
cookies, smoked fish,
alcohol, people acting stupid.
You had me at "clookies." I can't
wait to find out what they are.
What should I wear?
Oh, it's nice. It's real nice.
People get dressed up.
I will look so
handsome for you, Darryl.
Uh...
I'm gonna...
Dwight really wants my bonus.
He's trying to entrap me.
Oh, God, now I can't
drink at this thing.
I get really
pranky when I drink.
Erin, what can I get for you?
Do you have cola?
Kirkland, if you have it.
Why would you come to a bar
and ask for a cola
when you can get
some from the kitchen?
Did some small part of you want
something a little stronger?
Ryan, Kevin, Phyllis, Oscar,
come and take these shots.
Yes!
Will do.
The fifth one is for you, Erin.
You can take it or leave it.
To take it would be
to accept that you're
at a party,
and you're an adult woman
and you have
an adventurous spirit.
To leave it
would be fine, too.
One, two, three.
Yes.
Okay.
Wow!
Whoo!
Hey, hey, nice.
Jiminy Christmas!
Jiminy Christmas, indeed.
Hit her up.
Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
- Wow!
Yeah, I just got my
replacement credit card.
Do you want the number?
Oh, it's 4-7-9-3
O-O-3-2-3-3-1-3.
The security code is 9-2-7.
Okay, great,
thank you very much.
Bye.
So Dwight did take the bait.
He used my credit card numbers to
send a $200 bouquet of flowers
to my wife.
From me.
Boom!
Look, it's
Christmas, so you're allowed...
Hello.
I meant dressed up
compared to normal.
You usually dress
like a Ghostbuster.
Okay. I thought you'd
wear a sweater.
Since when does a sweater
mean "dressed up"?
Am I your grandson?
Come on, stay, all right?
It's good for people
to get to know you.
As a contestant on
Dancing with the Stars maybe.
I want my sugar-free cookie, and
then I want a sugar cookie.
And then I want my nap.
That's right.
Thank you.
She is remarkable.
Edgy impressions.
Thank you.
How many drinks
have you had tonight?
I can't be
driving everybody home.
A thousand.
Woah!
Maybe you should take a break.
Maybe you should
mind your own business.
Just kidding.
Ah! I've been attacked!
Oh, my God. Someone put a
porcupine in my drawer.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I was just sitting here at my
desk, and I reached into my drawer
to grab my toothbrush
and some tooth powder,
and all of a sudden,
I was attacked
by this bloodthirsty
rabid creature.
I wonder, in this office,
who has access to a porcupine?
Or who in this office
knows that I have access
and is trying to set me up?
Hmm. You know, this sounds
a lot like the premise
of my latest Chad
Flenderman novel,
A Murder for Framing.
Chad Flenderman. Just an
easy-going black guy who knows
the streets,
yet he also went to Oxford.
So just as comfortable on a
motorcycle as he is on Air Force One.
And he's also the world's
leading Egyptologist.
Toby, nobody cares about your
sex-crazed black detective.
No,no,no,no,no, women chase him.
He misses his wife.
Hello, lacerated
hand here, folks.
Nice try.
This is ridiculous.
Oh, is it really?
Two separate times
you have set me up to believe
that I was being
recruited by the CIA.
Three times, actually.
You see?
Jim, this has your
fingerprints all over it.
Andy, you've got
to be kidding me.
Fingerprints can be planted.
You know,
with a severed hand...
Do you think
that's what happened?
Do you think he
used a severed hand?
Okay, you know what, why don't
we just call Animal Control?
You might want to run that by Angela.
'Cause it's so cute.
No. Porcupines don't have souls.
They're like dogs.
Yes, I'm calling
from Dunder Mifflin.
We have a very rabid
porcupine in our office.
Someone should
come pick it up.
Come down right away.
I don't know, let me ask.
Were you quilled?
Yes, I was quilled.
And what's its name?
Henrietta.
Oh.
What? Uh...
All right. Get her
out of here, Dwight.
Hey.
Guys, I just wanted to say...
Come here.
I am so happy you
guys are together. Okay?
And you both have
such beautiful hair.
Thank you.
I hope you guys get married.
And who knows? Maybe at the
wedding, I meet someone.
Okay.
And later on tonight,
I hope I see you guys kiss.
Yay.
Okay, well, I'm gonna go do
another reverse spit.
That's how the cool
kids say "get a drink."
That's...
That's the girl you dated?
Yeah, she's not always
like that. It's...
No, she seems fun.
Yeah, excuse me.
Okay.
HEY
Have you had anything to eat
besides candy canes?
Every martini has an olive.
Okay.
Maybe I should make you
some oatmeal or something.
I don't want to put you out, but
if someone's making oatmeal,
I'll take an apple cinnamon
and a maple brown sugar
in one bowl with whole milk.
Hey, I never told
you my Christmas wish.
Okay.
It's about you.
That's not what it should be. It should
just be like a trinket or something.
It's that I wish
Jessica was dead.
You mean you wish
she wasn't here or something.
I wish she was in a graveyard
under the ground
with worms coming
out of her mouth.
Hey, you know,
you can't say that, okay?
That's my girlfriend
that you're talking about.
You and I are not
together anymore.
You need to get over it.
Take your wish back.
Too late.
It's already been wished.
And you promised it would come true.
You wrote it in an e-mail!
So which one are you,
a murderer or a liar?
HEY
So there was talk of oatmeal.
You know, don't listen
to what anyone is saying.
You look like a princess.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I was too embarrassed.
Hey, guys, sorry to interrupt.
I just found this on my desk
and need to talk to
somebody about it.
Can you believe that?
Is that Cece?
Yes, it is.
Oh, man.
That's awful.
Cece is Jim's daughter.
Oh, my God.
How could somebody do that?
I know. I mean,
the way I see it is,
you can deface
any picture of me.
Any one. Pick one.
Not my kid, though.
Who did this?
Do you know who did this?
I don't...
I know who did this. Dwight.
Dwight?
Yeah, he did.
What? No.
He should pay.
He is gonna pay.
This is fire-able.
- Okay.
- It's... I mean...
Let me just see
it one more time.
You know what?
I know who my friends are now.
But I shouldn't
have got you involved.
Because the truth is, I don't even
really care about this picture.
It's a little out of focus.
It was probably an accident,
right? Like...
That's no accident.
Right. You're right. So maybe it
was me who did it. By accident.
What?
I'll figure it out.
Get to the bottom of it.
Merry merry.
Enough of this garbage.
This is Christmas.
Christmas!
You all right, Santa?
You know those
movies where two friends
are sleeping
together and it's like,
hey, can they stay friends?
Yes.
Do you think two
friends who are
not sleeping
together can stay friends?
Two friends who are
not sleeping together,
can they remain friends?
Yes, yeah.
No. I... I don't know.
Okay.
By the WHY,
I'm not gonna mess with
your and Dwight's bonuses.
I think it's
causing more problems.
So just be yourselves,
have fun,
and try not to let
it affect your work.
All right.
I will definitely do that.
All right. I'll tell Dwight.
You know what?
You're sitting and thinking.
And it's probably better
if it comes from me anyway.
Christmas miracles do happen.
Yes, they totally do.
You can't click on
these Kardashian links.
That's why you
have so many viruses.
Well, help me, okay?
I'm trying, but...
You need to...
Kelly.
Yo. On it.
Game on.
I don't know what I was
thinking, it was awful. Awful.
Jessica, did you just fart?
And that is how it's done.
I would like another alcohol.
Let's you and I take a walk. Oscar,
you're in charge of the bar.
What? I haven't
bartended in forever.
Never considered
myself a mixologist.
Oh, this is daunting. Um, I
need a mortar, pestle, muddier.
Does anyone have any
chocolate shavings?
Your heart is broken.
So's mine.
And?
And what?
And do you have any
advice or anything...
Oh, my God.
...to help me feel better?
I've been married thrice,
and each
has ended in
an acrimonious divorce.
I'm not sure I'm the best
person to give love advice.
I was hoping you were going
to make me feel better.
When you do your makeup, how long
does it take usually? 'Cause...
It depends.
Chad Flenderman's
kryptonite...
Woah.
We got a real
Clarence Thomas here.
Hi.
I'll see you at home.
Okay. Okay, great.
Perfect.
Bye.
I still don't
get why you can't
just call her
a cab and pay for it.
I would, it just...
That wasn't the holiday wish.
Either he drives or I drive,
and now I'm drunk and mad.
Okay, We-
All right, come on, Meredith.
Bye. Thank you, Santa.
You bet.
Thank God Erin's getting
a ride home with Robert,
'cause she is trashed.
And who better to drive
her home than Robert?
I mean, what
a stand up guy, you know.
I mean, he's going through a lot.
Separating from his wife,
showing up at the Christmas party
in a track suit and a blazer.
Let's go, let's go.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Hang on.
All right.
Woah! My stuff!
What? What is all that?
It's my valuables!
It's junk.
This is my treasures.
No, they're my treasures!
You're a hoarder. My God!
No, I'm not!
I'm gonna sell it on eBay!
No, no, no, you be careful.
Be careful!
Ah! My Santa suit's stuck.
What are we gonna do with all
that bonus money, Henrietta,huh?
Where are we?
This ain't my street.
Oh. This is the posh
part of town, huh?
Oh, my God.
Wonder what a studio condo would
cost in this neighborhood.
Meredith, shut your
drunk hole right now.
Erin, it was
great fun tonight.
Take a few aspirin, drink a whole lot
of water, sleep in in the morning.
Thank you. Good night.
What are you smiling for?
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
I'm sure I am not.
Let's get you home.
Ow!
Take it easy!
Oh, man!
Fell asleep. Took a nap.
Hey, guys.
I feel refreshed now.
How's it going?
Dwight.
Took a little nap right next to Jim's desk.
I feel so good right now.
Mmm. Cookies.
What's everyone staring at?
Oh, man! I was supposed
to tell Dwight something.
Come on, Jim.
I got nothing.